NGUYEN THANH HOAI

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCES

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER TMA Solutions

02/2022 - 05/2022

- Learned about react, redux, vue
- Built CRUD and called API
- Designed the UI and event handlers

TESTERReal Time Analytics

01/2019 - 09/2019

- Developed and implemented inspection plans
- Keeped track of new requests from the project
- Prepared equipment for the software testing process
- Wrote documents about the project to customers
- Provided issues that the project required (software, hardware, resources) for Project Manager / Test Manager
- Created the form as required

SUMMARY

For 4 years of studying at Industrial University of Ho Chi Minh City, I had many opportunities to participate in web and mobile application projects using ReactJS such as Chat web and mobile app, hotel management web application.. I look forward to becoming a member of your company so that I can learn skills, experience and be able to accompany you for a long time. For more information see: -

https://github.com/NewTechnologyProject/WeeAllo

- https://github.com/se-graduation-thesis

CONTACT INFO

**** 0353784735

A hoai.se.iuh@gmail.com

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Vue JS, Java, Spring, Firebase, AWS

EDUCATIONS

INDUSTRIAL UNIVERSITY OF HCMC Software Engineering

08/2018 - 07/2022

Software engineering trains professional knowledge links to the software development process to produce high quality software products that meet the specific requirements of the manufacturing platform. association platform. I am equipped with in-depth knowledge



of software companies, including: software development process, skills to operate software tools to support the development of other software. In addition, also equipped with the necessary knowledge related to the work performed in a project software such as: requirements collection, analysis, design, programming, testing, operation and software maintenance.